module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Where does Abbi work (seasons 1 â€“ 3) in Broad City?',
    a: 'Jumbo Juice',
    b: 'Soulstice',
    c: 'Dave & Busters',
    d: 'Booklyn',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which house does Tyrion belong to in Game of Thrones?',
    a: 'Lannister',
    b: 'Stark',
    c: 'Targaryen',
    d: 'Bolton',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which TV host was NOT formerly a correspondent for the Daily Show?',
    a: 'John Oliver',
    b: 'Samantha Bee',
    c: 'Stephen Colbert',
    d: 'Seth Meyers',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the fictional corporation that runs 'Westworld'?",
    a: 'Forde',
    b: 'Centurii',
    c: 'Delos',
    d: 'Blackhat',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What theme park is down the street from Bobs Burgers?',
    a: 'Wonder Wharf',
    b: 'Dolphin Dock',
    c: 'Pookah Park',
    d: 'Water Walk',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'In season 1 of Atlanta, which item is successfully exchanged for a dog?',
    a: 'painting',
    b: 'samurai sword',
    c: '2 pirate coins',
    d: 'storage locker key',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: "What is The Marvelous Ms. Maisel's first name?",
    a: 'Anne',
    b: 'Midge',
    c: 'Yael',
    d: 'Rachel',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which Marvel TV show was NOT cancelled this year?',
    a: 'Daredevil',
    b: 'Luke Cage',
    c: 'Iron Fist',
    d: 'All were cancelled',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: "In the show Homecoming, what is Julia Roberts' occupation?",
    a: 'Neurosurgeon',
    b: 'Lobbyist',
    c: 'Caseworker',
    d: 'Hypnotist',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is NOT a curse word substitute on The Good Place?",
    a: 'Fork',
    b: 'Shirtballs',
    c: 'Here',
    d: 'Pez',
    answer: 'd'
  },
];